Well, the invocation says bye, hope you are fine chief, Mr. Christian.
Heavenly Father, we are thankful for you, we are thankful for the leaders you provide for us to miss us.
You will be with them as they discuss and make decisions for them. You will be meeting them tonight.
And your name will be great.
Amen.
I'm pleased to lead us to our voice guides.
I'd like to lead you just to come back from United States of America.
You will be with them as they discuss and understand one nation and under God.
And if it is, whatever you need, that's just for all.
Thank you, Jimmy.
Four of us get the personal appearances.
Five claims list.
Make a motion. We approve.
Second.
He said five.
Don't go.
All right.
Five.
Six.
May that's when the February 5th, 2024, regular meeting.
Motion.
Second.
All right.
Thank you.
Seven.
They've described to remain claim for Pensacola, GRDA,
Re licensing and associated complaint proceedings in the amount of 16,975,
20 cents.
So may I remember the counsel you have an invoice in your packet.
For David's right to remain.
For professional services and disbursements incurred December 4th,
2023 through December 28.
On behalf of the city focused on remaining pleadings,
filings and other documentation, preparing responses there to
communicating.
With the mime team related to the following.
These are damn safety issues.
Relicents.
Extudity plan.
Contaminated.
Settlement transport study.
Enhuff amendment.
And the Circuit Court of Appeals.
Follow-up.
If the 16,975 dollars in 20 cents is approved.
In that budget of originally 750,000.
If that is approved, we would have remaining balance of 525,933 dollars
or 75 cents for this fiscal year.
Motion to approve.
Sorry.
All right.
Hey.
Good ill-stratten Edmunds and Palmer Klein for GRDA.
Relaxing seeing in the amount of 1,590 dollars.
All right.
I can't say you have an invoice for good ill-stratten.
For professional services and disbursements incurred from December 21, 2023 through
January 19th of 2024.
These issues related to the day of licensing issues.
Realistic study plan.
Contaminated.
Settlement transport study.
Enhuff amendment.
And the Circuit Court of Appeals.
Follow-up.
If you approve this $1,590,
an expended from the $750,000 budget,
that would leave us $524,343,755 since this fiscal year.
Much to approve.
Second.
Williams.
Hi.
Doctor.
Now, master service agreement with Anderson Engineering
owned for the Engineering Service,
for Engineering Services.
Public office.
Yes, sir.
So this is renewing Anderson Engineering,
or they changed their name to, um,
so this is for engineering there, um,
contract to do engineering services.
It's also on the city side, too.
So, same people?
Yes, sir.
This changed me.
That's actually been on their trucks for a while.
Yeah.
So you have some of those guys with you that I want to say.
I think good.
Happy to.
I'd like to appreciate the opportunity to have a few years experience
for individuals that, um, appreciate the opportunity
for these projects, and we can get that with you.
I'd like to add, they do a great job.
I don't think, uh, Tyler could do without them.
Sorry.
I appreciate it, man.
I'm sorry.
You're right here.
Much to approve.
Second.
Williams.
Hi.
He's dead.
So cool.
Hi.
Parker.
10.
Workborder authorization number two
with Anderson Engineering owned for the solid waste management.
Alternatives evaluation, not to exceed 37,000 and $50.
So we had previously talked about this at our session in our
construction set committee.
So this is a recorder for them to do a high level study with
burns in my mouth to determine, you know, if we build a new
transfer station or we will be doing a city of length of revenue
status expenses, I did what I think right for the best when we said,
I think we don't know what we don't know about the length of
the, uh, for experts to do this.
Yeah, I'm trying to see what they're going to work with.
Yeah, I think this is a study that has to be done and that we really have a
choice at this point with the, with the rights that continue to go out for us
transferring to somewhere else.
I mean, we definitely need an alternative.
Yeah.
As part of their study, and we talk about even outside that they are going to
I'll make a motion to approve.
Okay.
Parker.
Hi.
William.
He's set.
Hi.
You're staying up there, aren't you?
We'll have an acknowledge of Oklahoma Department of Armoured on Fawlety.
Permit.
Number WL00505-823-0861 for the construction of 995 Linear Feet.
The 6-inch ADPE.
Waterline plus.
All the accessories.
The serve.
The Q Street.
Southwest.
Waterline.
Extension.
So we have no load on this.
Just as far the DQ program.
We have to acknowledge.
Technology.
Good.
12 of the new business of any of which is represents the posting of this agenda.
13 staff reports.
14.
We can be an announcement.
15 adjournment.
Motion.
Second.
You can't talk.
So.
Hi.
William.
Parker.